Guide to the Samuel Stark Film stills: photographs, 1925-1972
Department of Special Collections
Samuel Stark Film stills: photographs.,
1925-1972
MSS PHOTO 172
Stark, Samuel
6.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Samuel Stark, 1969.
Provenance
Originally part of the Stanford Libraries Theater Collection.Gift of Samuel Stark, 1969.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Some 1,102 movies are represented, many with more than one photo.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Motion pictures--United States--History.; Photoprints.; Theater Collection.
Collection Contents
- 1. "Aaron Slick From Punkin Crik" 1952 (Box 1)
  Dinah Shore, Alan Young
- 2. "Abie's Irish Rose" 1946 (Box 1)
  with Michael Chekhov
- 3. "Accused of Murder". (Box 1)
- 4. "Achilles" (Box 1)
  Gordon Mitchell, Jacques Bergerac
- 5. "Adventures of Huckleberry Finn", Eddie Hodges, Archie (Box 1)
- 6. "Advise & Consent" (Box 1)
  Henry Fonda, Charles Laughton
- 7. "Affairs of Anatole" 1936 (Box 1)
  Wallace Reid, Wanda Hawley
- 8. "The Affairs of Cellini" 1934 (Box 1)
  Fredric March, Constance Bennett
- 9. "After the Storm" 1928 (Box 1)
  Hobart Bosworth, Eugenia Gilbert
- 10. "Age of Indiscretion" (Box 1)
  Pierre Michel Beck, Marina Vlady
- 11. "Ain`t Misbehavin'" (Box 1)
  Rory Calhoun, Piper Laurie
- 12. "Alaska Seas" (Box 1)
  Robert Ryan, Jan Sterling
- 13. "Al Capone" (Box 1)
  Rod Steiger, Fay Spain
- 14. "Alfie" (Box 1)
  Jane Asher, Sydney Tafler
- 15. "Alfred the Great" (Box 1)
  David Hemmings, Michael York,
- 16. "Algiers" (Box 1)
  Charles Boyer, Hedy Lamarr
- 17. "Ali Baba & the Forty Thieves" (Box 1)
  Maria Montez, Jon Hall
- 18. "Alimony" 1936 (Box 1)
  Warner Baxter, Ruby Miller
- 19. "All Fall Down" (Box 1)
  Eva Marie Saint, Warren Beatty, Karl
- 20. "All For Mary" (Box 1)
  Nigel Patrick, Kathleen Harrison
- 21. "All Mine To Give" 1957, 15 (Box 1)
  Cameron Mitchell, Glynis Johns
- 22. "All That Heaven Allows" (Box 1)
  Rock Hudson, Jane Wyman
- 23. "All That Money Can Buy" 1941 (Box 1)
- 24. "All The King's Horses" 1934 (Box 1)
  Carl Brisson, Mary Ellis
- 25. "Almost Married" (Box 1)
  Piper Laurie, Tony Curtis
- 26. "Alvarez Kelly" (Box 1)
  William Holden, Richard Widmark
- 27. "The Ambassador's Daughter" (Box 1)
  Olivia de Havilland, John
- 28. "The Ambushers" (Box 1)
  Dean Martin, Senta Berger
- 29. "And Now Tomorrow" (Box 1)
  Alan Ladd, Susan Hayward, Loretta Young
- 30. "And Soon The Darkness" (Box 1)
  Sandor Ellis, Pamela Franklin
- 31. "Angel of Mercy" 1936 (Box 1)
  Kay Francis
- 32. "Angels in the Outfield" 1951 (Box 1)
- 33. "Angels One Five" (Box 1)
  John Gregory
- 34. "Angels With Dirty Faces" (Box 1)
  James Cagney
- 35. "Anne of the Indies" (Box 1)
- 36. "Apache Ambush" (Box 1)
  Bill Williams, Richard Jaeckel
- 37. "Appointment in Honduras" (Box 1)
  Glenn Ford, Ann Sheridan
- 38. "Arabesque" (Box 1)
  Gregory Peck, Sophia Loren
- 39. "Arabian Nights" 1942 (Box 1)
  Jon Hall
- 40. "Are Husbands Necessary?" 1939 (Box 1)
  (name later changed to "My Love )
- 41. "Arkansas Traveler" 1938 (Box 1)
  Bob Burns, Fay Bainter
- 42. "Around the Corner" (Box 1)
  Charlie Murray, George Sidney
- 43. "Artists and Models" (Box 1)
  Jack Benny, Gail Patrick, Ida Lupino
- 44. "Assignment in China" (Box 1)
  Virginia Bruce, William Lundigan
- 45. "At Long Last Love" 1975 (Box 1)
  Eileen Brennan, Cybill Shepherd, Madeline Kahn, Burt Reynolds
- 46. "The Atomic City" (Box 1)
  Gene Barry, Lydia Clarke
- 47. "Attila the Hun" (Box 1)
  Anthony Quinn, Sophia Loren
- 48. "Avanti!" 1972 (Box 1)
  Jack Lemmon, Juliet Mills
- 49. "The Awful Truth" 1937 (Box 1)
  Irene Dunne
- 50. "Babes in Toyland" (Box 1)
  Annette Funicello, Tommy Sands, Roy Bolger
- 51. "Back To God's Country" (Box 1)
  Rock Hudson, Marcia Henderson
- 52. "The Bad Lord Byron" (Box 1)
- 53. "The Bad Man of Brimstone" (Box 1)
  Dennis O'Keefe
- 54. "Bed Men of Missouri" (Box 1)
  Jane Wyman, Dennis Morgan
- 55. "The Balcony" (Box 1)
  Lee Grant, Shelley Winters
- 56. "The Bandit of Sherwood Forest" (Box 1)
  Cornel Wilde
- 57. "Banjo On My Knee" 1937 (Box 1)
  Barbara Stanwyck, Joel McCrea
- 58. "Barbary Coast" 1935 (Box 1)
  Edward G. Robinson, Miriam Hopkins
- 59. "The Battle for Anzio" (Box 1)
  Robert Mitchum, Peter Falk
- 60. "The Beachcomber" (Box 1)
  Glynis Johns, Robert Newton
- 61. "Beau Brummel" (Box 1)
  John Barrymore, Mary Astor
- 62. "Beau Chumps" (Box 1)
  Laurel and Hardy
- 63. "Beau Geste" 1939 (Box 1)
  Gary Cooper, Ray Milland, Susan Hayward
- 64. "Beau Geste" 1966 (Box 1)
  Guy Stockwell, Doug McClure, Leslie Nielsen
- 65. "Beauty and the Barge" (Box 1)
  Gordon Harker
- 66. "The Bedford Incident" (Box 1)
  Richard Widmark, Sidney Poitier
- 67. "Behind Office Doors" 1931 (Box 1)
  Ricardo Cortez, Mary Astor
- 68. "Behind the Rising Sun" (Box 1)
  J. Carrol Naish, Tom Neal
- 69. "Behold My Wife" 1934 (Box 1)
  Sylvia Sidney, Gene Raymond
- 70. "Belle of the Nineties" (Box 1)
  Mae West
- 71. "Belle of the Yukon" 1944 (Box 1)
  Gypsy Rose Lee, Randolph Scott, Dinah Shore
- 72. "Belles On Their Toes" (Box 1)
  Myrna Loy, Jeanne Crain
- 73. "Bells Are Ringing" (Box 1)
  Judy Holliday, Dean Martin
- 74. "The Beloved Rogue" 1928 (Box 1)
  John Barrymore
- 75. "Below the Sahara" (Box 2)
- 76. "Bengal Rifles" (Box 2)
  Rock Hudson, Arlene Dahl
- 77. "Ben Hur" 1959 (Box 2)
  Charlton Heston, Jack Hawkins
- 78. "The Benny Goodman Story" (Box 2)
  Steve Allen, Donna Reed
- 79. "Betrayed" (Box 2)
  Clark Gable, Lana Turner, Victor Mature
- 80. "Beyond Mombasa" (Box 2)
  Cornel Wilde, Donna Reed
- 81. "Beyond Shanghai" (Box 2)
- 82. "The Bible" 1966 (Box 2)
  ("Noah's Ark", 1929)
- 83. "The Bicycle Thief" (Box 2)
- 84. "The Big Bluff" (Box 2)
  John Bromfield, Martha Vickers
- 85. "The Big Broadcast of 1937" 1937 (Box 2)
  Martha Raye, Benny Goodman
- 86. "Big Brown Eyes" 1936 (Box 2)
  Cary Grant, Joan Bennett
- 87. "The Big Chief" 1960 (Box 2)
  Fernandel
- 88. "The Big Country" (Box 2)
  Gregory Peck, Jean Simmons, Charlton Heston
- 89. "A Big Hand for the Little Lady" (Box 2)
  Henry Fonda, Joanne Woodward, Jason Robards
- 90. "The Big Money" (Box 2)
  Ian Carmichael, Kathleen Harrison
- 91. "The Big Parade" 1931 (Box 2)
  Renee Adoree, John Gilbert
- 92. "The Big Steal" 1949 (Box 2)
  Robert Mitchum
- 93. "The Big Wheel" (Box 2)
  Mickey Rooney, Thomas Mitchell
- 94. "A Bill of Divorcement" (Box 2)
  John Barrymore, Billie Burke
- 95. "Billy Liar" (Box 2)
  Tom Courtenay, Julie Christie
- 96. "The Bird of Paradise" 1932 (Box 2)
  Delores Del Rio
- 97. "The Birds" 1965 (Box 2)
  Rod Taylor, Tippi Henren, Suzanne Pleshette, Jessica Tandy
- 98. "Bitter Harvest" (Box 2)
  Janet Munro, John Stride
- 99. "The Black Cat" (Box 2)
  Boris Karloff, Bela Lugosi
- 100. "Black Narcissus" (Box 2)
  Deborah Kerr, Sabu, Jean Simmons
- 101. "The Black Room Mystery" 1935 (Box 2)
  Boris Karloff, Marian Marsh,
- 102. "The Black Shield of Falworth" 1954 (Box 2)
  Tony Curtis, Janet Leigh, Claud Allister
- 103. "Black Tuesday" (Box 2)
  Edward G. Robinson
- 104. "Blackbeard the Pirate" (Box 2)
  Robert Newton
- 105. "Blackbeard's Ghost" (Box 2)
  Peter Ustinov, Dean Jones, Suzanne Pleshette
- 106. "Blindfold" (Box 2)
  Rock Hudson, Claudia Cardinale
- 107. "Bloodhounds of Broadway" (Box 2)
  Mitzi Gaynor, Scott Brady
- 108. "The Blue Dahlia" (Box 2)
  Alan Ladd, Veronica Lake, William Bendix
- 109. "The Blue Max" (Box 2)
  George Peppard, James Mason, Ursula Andress
- 110. "Boccaccio '70" 1970 (Box 2)
  Sophia Loren, Romy Schneider
- 111. "The Bold and the Brave" (Box 2)
  Wendell Corey, Mickey Rooney
- 112. "Bolero" 1933 (Box 2)
  George Raft, Carole Lombard
- 113. "Bonnie and Clyde" 1967 (Box 2)
  Faye Dunaway, Warren Beatty
- 114. "Borderline" (Box 2)
  Fred MacMurray, Claire Trevor
- 115. "Born to Dance" (Box 2)
  Eleanor Powell
- 116. "The Bottom of the World" (Box 2)
- 117. "The Bowery Princess" (Box 2)
  Shirley Temple, Frank Morgan
- 118. "Bowery to Broadway" 1944 (Box 2)
  Louise Allbritton, Thomas Gomez
- 119. "The Boy and the Bridge" (Box 2)
  Ian Maclaine, Liam Redmond
- 120. "Boys Town" (Box 2)
  Spencer Tracy, Mickey Rooney
- 121. "The Bride of Frankenstein" (Box 2)
  Elsa Lanchester
- 122. "Bride of the Regiment" 1930 (Box 2)
  Myrna Loy
- 123. "Bridge on the River Kwai" (Box 2)
  William Holden, Jack Hawkings, Alec Guinness
- 124. "The Bright Road" (Box 2)
  Tanya Morozova, L. Orlova
- 125. "Brink of Hell" (Box 2)
  William Holden
- 126. "Broadway Melody of 1937" 1937 (Box 2)
  Eleanor Powell, Robert Taylor
- 127. "Broadway Through A Keyhole" (Box 2)
  Walter Winchell, Texas Guinan, Blossom Seeley
- 128. "Broken Blossoms" (Box 2)
  Richard Barthelmess. Lillian Gish
- 129. "Bronco Buster" (Box 2)
  John Lund, Scott Brady
- 130. "Brother Rat" (Box 2)
  Wayne Morris, Priscilla Lane
- 131. "Brown of Harvard" (Box 2)
  William Haines, Mary Brian
- 132. "Brute Force" (Box 2)
  Burt Lancaster, Hume Cronyn
- 133. "Buccaneer's Girl" (Box 2)
  Yvonne De Carlo, Philip Friend
- 134. "Bulldog Drummond" (Box 2)
  Ronald Colman, Claude Allister
- 135. "Bulldog Drummond in Africa" (Box 2)
  John Howard, Heather Angel
- 136. "Bullets or Ballots" 1936 (Box 2)
  Edward G. Robinson, Humphrey
- 137. "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid" 1969 (Box 2)
  Paul Newman, Robert Redford, Katharine Ross
- 138. "By The Light of the Silvery Moon"1953 (Box 2)
- 139. "Cafe Society" 1938 (Box 2)
  Madeleine Carroll, Fred MacMurray
- 140. "Call Me Bwana" (Box 2)
  Bob Hope, Anita Ekberg
- 141. "The Call of the North" 1921 (Box 2)
  Noah Beery, Madge Bellamy
- 142. "Camelot" 1967 (Box 2)
  Richard Harris, Vanessa Redgrave
- 143. "Can Can" (Box 2)
  Frank Sinatra, Shirley MacLaine, Maurice Chevalier, Louis Jourdan
- 144. " The Canary Murder Case" 1929 (Box 2)
  William Powell, Jean Author
- 145. "Can't Help Singing" 1944 (Box 2)
- 146. "A Canterbury Tale" (Box 2)
  Eric Portman, Sheila Sim
- 147. "Caprice Espagnol" 1935 (Box 2)
  Marlene Dietrich, Lionel Atwill
- 148. "Captain From Castile" (Box 2)
  Tyrone Power
- 149. "Captain China" (Box 2)
  John Payne, Gail Russell
- 150. "Captain Fury" 1939 (Box 2)
  Claude Allister
- 151. "The Capture" 1950 (Box 2)
  Theresa Wright
- 152. "Carlton-Browne of the F. O." (Box 2)
  Terry-Thomas, Peter Sellers
- 153. "Carolina" 1934 (Box 2)
  Lionel Barrymore
- 154. "Carousel" (Box 2)
  Gordon MacRae, Shirley Jones
- 155. "The Carpetbaggers" (Box 2)
  George Peppard
- 156. "Carrington V. C." (Box 3)
  David Niven, Margaret Leighton
- 157. "Carry On Cabby" (Box 3)
  Sidney James, Hattie Jacques
- 158. "Carry On Cleo" (Box 3)
  Sidney James, Kenneth Williams
- 159. "The Case Against Brooklyn" (Box 3)
  Darren McGavin, Maggie Hayes
- 160. "The Case of Express Delivery" (Box 3)
  Clifford Evans, Donals Houston
- 161. "Casino Royale" (Box 3)
  Peter Sellers, Ursula Andress, David Niven
- 162. "Cass Timberlane" (Box 3)
  Spencer Tracy, Lana Turner
- 163. "Cast A Giant Shadow" (Box 3)
  Kirk Douglas, Yul Brynner
- 164. "The Cat and the Canary" (Box 3)
- 165. "Catherine the Great" 1934 (Box 3)
  Douglas Fairbanks, Jr., Elizabeth Bergner
- 166. "The Cat's Paw" 1934 (Box 3)
  Harold Lloyd, Una Merkel
- 167. "The Challenge" (Box 3)
  Jayne Mansfield, Anthony Quayle
- 168. "The Champagne Murders" (Box 3)
  Anthony Perkins, Maurice Ronet
- 169. "Champagne Waltz" 1936 (Box 3)
  Gladys Swarthout
- 170. "Channel Crossing" (Box 3)
  Matheson Lang, Constance Cummings
- 171. "Charade" (Box 3)
  Cary Grant, Audrey Hepburn
- 172. "The Charge At Feather River" (Box 3)
  Guy Madison, Frank Lovejoy
- 173. "The Charge of the Light Brigade" (Box 3)
  Trevor Howard
- 174. "The Chase" (Box 3)
  Marlon Brando, Jane Fonda, Robert Redford
- 175. "Che!" (Box 3)
  Omar Sharif, Jack Palance
- 176. "The Cheat" 1924 (Box 3)
  Sessue Hayakawa, Hannie Ward
- 177. "Check and Double Check" (Box 3)
  Amos 'n' Andy (Freeman Gosden, Charles Correll)
- 178. "Chicago Deadline" (Box 3)
  Donna Reed, Alan Ladd
- 179. "Chicago Masquerade" (Box 3)
  Rhonda Fleming, Mark Stevens
- 180. "El Cid" (Box 3)
  Charlton Heston
- 181. "The Cincinnati Kid" (Box 3)
  Steve McQueen, Edward G. Robinson, Ann-Margret
- 182. "The Circus" (Box 3)
  Charlie Chaplin, Merna Kennedy
- 183. "Circus Days" 1923 (Box 3)
  Jackie Coogan, Russell Simpson
- 184. "The Cisco Kid" 1935 (Box 3)
  Warner Baxter
- 185. "The Citadel" (Box 3)
  Robert Donat, Rosalind Russell
- 186. "City Lights" 1930 (Box 3)
  Charlie Chaplin
- 187. "City Under The Sea" (Box 3)
  Vincent Price, Tab Hunter
- 188. "Cleopatra" 1934 (Box 3)
  Claudette Colbert, Henry Wilcoxon
- 189. "The Climax" 1944 (Box 3)
- 190. "Cocoanut Grove" 1938 (Box 3)
  Fred MacMurray, Harriet Hilliard
- 191. "Cohens and Kellys in Scotland" (Box 3)
  Charles Murray, George Sidney
- 192. "College Confidential" (Box 3)
  Steve Allen, Jayne Meadows, Walter Winchell, Mamie Van Doren
- 193. "College Holiday" 1936 (Box 3)
  Martha Raye, Jack Benny
- 194. "College Scandal" 1935 (Box 3)
  Wendy Barrie
- 195. "Collegiate" 1935 (Box 3)
  Joe Penner, Jack Oakie, Betty Grable
- 196. "Comanche Territory" (Box 3)
  Maureen O'Hara, Macdonald Carey
- 197. "Come Back, Little Sheba" (Box 3)
  Burt Lancaster, Shirley Booth
- 198. "Come September" (Box 3)
  Rock Hudson, Gina Lollobrigida
- 199. "The Comedians" (Box 3)
  Richard Burton, Elizabeth Taylor
- 200. "The Comedy of Life" (Box 3)
  Milton Sills, Maria Corda
- 201. "Congo Crossing" (Box 3)
  Virginia Mayo, Peter Lorre
- 202. "The Conquering Power" (Box 3)
  Rudolph Valentino
- 203. "The Conqueror" 1956 (Box 3)
  John Wayne, Susan Hayward, Thomas Gomez
- 204. "Conspiracy of Hearts" (Box 3)
  Lilli Palmer, Sylvia Sims
- 205. "The Constant Nymph" (Box 3)
  Charles Boyer, Joan Fontaine
- 206. "Cop Hater" (Box 3)
  Robert Loggia, Gerald O'Loughlin
- 207. "Corvette K-225" 1943 (Box 3)
  Robert Mitchum, Barry Fitzgerald
- 208. "Cotton Queen" (Box 3)
- 209. "The County Seat" 1931 (Box 3)
  Charles Sale, Aileen Carlyle
- 210. "Cowboy" (Box 3)
  Glenn Ford, Jack Lemmon
- 211. "Crackdown" (Box 3)
  Carla Balenda, Bill Williams, Steve Flagg
- 212. "Crime Doctor", Warner Baxter, Margaret Lindsay (Box 3)
- 213. "Crime Doctor's Strangest Case" (Box 3)
- 214. "The Crooked Sky" (Box 3)
  Wayne Morris, Karin Booth
- 215. "The Cruel Sea" (Box 3)
  Donald Sinden
- 216. "Cry From The Streets" 1962 (Box 3)
  Max Bygraves, Barbara Murray
- 217. "Cry, The Beloved Country" (Box 3)
  Canada Lee, Charles
- 218. "A Cuckoo in the Nest" 1942 (Box 3)
  Tom Walls, Ralph Lynn
- 219. "Curly Top" (Box 3)
  John Boles, Shirley Temple
- 220. "Czar of Broadway" 1930 (Box 3)
  Claud Allister
- 221. "Daddy's Gone A'Huntin'" 1969 (Box 3)
  Carol White, Scott Hylands
- 222. "Daltons Ride Again" (Box 3)
- 223. "Dam on the Yellow River" (Box 3)
  Anita Ekberg, George Marshall
- 224. "The Damned" (Box 3)
  Macdonald Carey, Shirley Anne Field
- 225. "The Dancer of Marrakesh" (Box 3)
  Siren Adjemova, Yves Vincent
- 226. "Dancing in the Dark" 1948 (Box 3)
  William Powell, Mark Stevens, Betsy Drake
- 227. "Dangerous Curves" 1929 (Box 3)
  Richard Arlen, Clara Bow
- 228. "Dangerous When Wet" (Box 3)
  Esther Williams, Fernando Lamas
- 229. "The Dark Angel" 1935 (Box 3)
  Merle Oberon, Fredric March, Claud Allister
- 230. "Dark Waters" (Box 3)
- 231. "David Harum" (Box 3)
  Will Rogers, Stepin Fetchit
- 232. "The Day of the Dolphin" 1973 (Box 3)
  George C. Scott
- 233. "Deadlier Than The Male" (Box 3)
  Richard Johnson, Elke Sommer
- 234. "The Deadly Affair" (Box 3)
  James Mason, Maximillian Schell
- 235. "Dear John" (Box 3)
  Christina Schollin, Jare Kulle
- 236. "Dear Mr. Prohack" (Box 3)
  Cecil Parker, Glynis Johns
- 237. "Death Goes To School" (Box 3)
  Barbara Murray, Gordon Jackson
- 238. "Decline and Fall of a Bird Watcher" (Box 3)
  Felix Aylmer, Colin Blakely, Rober Harris
- 239. "Deputy from the Baltic" (Box 3)
  N. Cherkasov
- 240. "Derby Day" (Box 3)
  Anna Neagle, Michael Wilding, Googie Withers
- 241. "Desert Hawk" 1950 (Box 3)
  Yvonne De Carlo
- 242. "Desert Mice" (Box 3)
  Alfred James, Sidney James, Patricia Brendin
- 243. "Desert Sands" (Box 3)
  Ralph Meeker, Marla English
- 244. "Desperate Moment" (Box 3)
  Theodore Bikel, Albert Lieven
- 245. "The Detective" (Box 3)
  Frank Sinatra, Lee Remick
- 246. "The Devil and Miss Jones" (Box 3)
  Robert Cummings, Jean Author
- 247. "The Devil is a Woman" 1935 (Box 3)
- 248. "Devil With Women" 1930 (Box 3)
  Charles Farrell, Estelle Taylor
- 249. "Devil's Cargo" (Box 3)
  John Calvert, Rochelle Hudson
- 250. "Diamond Cut Diamond" 1932 (Box 3)
  Adolph Menjou, Claud Allister
- 251. "The Dictator" 1935 (Box 4)
  Madeleine Carroll
- 252. "The Disorderly Orderly" 1964 (Box 4)
  Jerry Lewis
- 253. "Don't Bother to Knock" (Box 4)
  Richard Todd, Nicole Maurey, Elke Sommer
- 254. "Don't Panic Chaps" (Box 4)
  Dennis Price, George Cole
- 255. "The Docks of New York" (Box 4)
- 256. "Doctor in Clover" (Box 4)
  Leslie Phillips, James Robertson Justice
- 257. "Doctor In Distress" (Box 4)
  Dirk Bogarde, Samantha Eggar,
- 258. "Dr. Jekyll & Mr. Hyde" (Box 4)
  Nila Naldi, John Barrymore
- 259. "Dr. No" 1965 (Box 4)
  Sean Connery, Ursula Andress
- 260. "Dr. Strangelove" (Box 4)
  Peter Sellers, George C. Scott
- 261. "Dodge City" (Box 4)
  Errol Flynn, Olivia de Havilland, Ann Sheridan
- 262. "A Dog's Life" 1928 (Box 4)
- 263. "Don Juan" (Box 4)
- 264. "Don Q, Son of Zorro" 1925 (Box 4)
  Douglas Fairbanks, Mary Astor
- 265. "The Donovan Affair" 1929 (Box 4)
  Jack Holt, Dorothy Revier
- 266. "Dorothy Vernon of Haddon Hall" 1924 (Box 4)
  Mary Pickford
- 267. "Down Memory Lane" (Box 4)
  Bing Crosby, Gloria Swanson, Ben Turpin, W.C.Fields, the Mack Sennett Bathing Beauties
- 268. "Dracula" (Box 4)
  Bela Lugosi, Helen Chandler
- 269. "Dragon Seed" (Box 4)
- 270. "Dramatic School" (Box 4)
  Luise Rainer, Alan Marshall, Paulette Goddard, Lana Turner
- 271. "Drum Crazy: The Gene Krupa Story" (Box 4)
  Sal Mineo
- 272. "The Drums of Love" (Box 4)
  Lionel Barrymore, Mary Philbin
- 273. "DUffy" (Box 4)
  Susannah York, James Mason, James Coburn
- 274. "Dugan of the Dugouts" 1928 (Box 4)
  Pauline Garron, Danny O'Shea
- 275. "The Duke Steps Out" (Box 4)
  William Haines, Eddie Nugent, Joan Crawford
- 276. "Dusty Ermine" (Box 4)
  Ronald Squire, Jane Baxter
- 277. "Each Dawn I Die" (Box 4)
  James Cagney, George Raft, Jane Bryan
- 278. "The Eagle" (Box 4)
  Rudolph Valentino, Vilma Banky
- 279. "The Eagle and the Hawk" 1933 (Box 4)
  Fredric March, Cary Grant
- 280. "Early to Bed" 1936 (Box 4)
  Mary Boland, Charlie Ruggles
- 281. "East of Borneo" 1931 (Box 4)
  Charles Bickford
- 282. "Easy Come, Easy Go" 1946 (Box 4)
  Barry Fitzgerald, Diana Lynn
- 283. "Easy Rider" (Box 4)
  Dennis Hopper, Peter Fonda, Jack Nicholson
- 284. "80,000 Suspects" (Box 4)
  Claire Bloom, Richard Johnson
- 285. "Elephant Walk" (Box 4)
  Elizabeth Taylor, Peter Finch
- 286. "The Enchanted Cottage" 1945 (Box 4)
- 287. "The Enchanted Hill" 1926 (Box 4)
  Florence Vidor, George Bancroft, Jack Holt, Mary Brian
- 288. "Escapade in Japan" 1957 (Box 4)
  Theresa Wright, Cameron Mitchell, Roger Makagawa
- 289. "Escape From Fort Bravo" (Box 4)
  William Holden, Eleanor Parkes, John Forsythe
- 290. "Escape Me Never" 1935 (Box 4)
  Elizabeth Bergner
- 291. "Escapement" (Box 4)
  Rod Cameron, Mary Murphy, Carl Jaffe
- 292. "Eternal Love" 1929 (Box 4)
  John Barrymore, Camilla Horn
- 293. "The Eternal Sea" (Box 4)
  Sterling Hayden, Alexis Smith
- 294. "Evangeline" (Box 4)
  Viola Barry
- 295. "Everything But the Truth" (Box 4)
  John Forsythe, Maureen O'Hara
- 296. "Everything Is Thunder" (Box 4)
- 297. "Evolution" (Box 4)
  May Irwin, John C. Rice
- 298. "Executioner on the Seas" (Box 4)
  Richard Harrison, Michele Mercier
- 299. "Exodus" (Box 4)
- 300. "Expresso Bongo" 1962 (Box 4)
  Laurence Harvey, Sylvia Syms
- 301. "Eyewitness" (Box 4)
  Donald Sinden, Muriel Pavlow
- 302. "Fahrenheit 451" (Box 4)
  Julie Christie, Oskar Werner
- 303. "The Fall of the Roman Empire" 1965 (Box 4)
  Sophia Loren, Steven Boyd, Alec Guinness, James Mason, Christopher Plummer
- 304. "Falling For You" 1942 (Box 4)
  Jack Hulbert, Cicely Courtneidge
- 305. "The False Madonna" 1932 (Box 4)
  Kaye Francis, William Boyd, Conway Tearle
- 306. "Fan-Fan La Tulipe" (Box 4)
  Gerard Philipe, Gina Lollobrigida
- 307. "Farewell Again" (Box 4)
  Leslie Banks, Flora Robson
- 308. "Fascinating Youth" (Box 4)
  Buddy Rogers, Josephine Dunne
- 309. "Father Goose" (Box 4)
  Cary Grant, Leslie Caron
- 310. "The Female Animal" 1957 (Box 4)
  Hedy Lamarr, Jane Powell, George Nader
- 311. "Ferry to Hong Kong" (Box 4)
  Curt Jurgens, Orson Welles, Sylvia Syms
- 312. "Fiddler on the Roof" 1971 (Box 4)
- 313. "55 Days at Peking" (Box 4)
  Charlton Heston, Ava Gardner, David Niven
- 314. "The Fighting Sullivans" (Box 4)
  Anne Baxter, Thomas Mitchell
- 315. "The Final Column" (Box 4)
  Sandra Dorne, Brian Worth
- 316. "Finders Keepers" (Box 4)
  Cliff Richard, The Shadows
- 317. "Five Graves to Cairo" (Box 4)
  Franchot Tone, Anne Baxter
- 318. "Flame in the Streets" (Box 4)
  John Mills, Sylvia Syms
- 319. "Flight" 1929 (Box 4)
  Jack Holt, Lila Lee
- 320. "Follow That Camel" (Box 4)
  Phil Silvers, Kenneth Williams
- 321. "Folly to be Wise" (Box 4)
  Alastair Sim
- 322. "For Heaven's Sake" (Box 4)
  Harold Lloyd, Jobyna Ralston
- 323. "Force of Evil" (Box 4)
  John Garfield, Beatrice Pearson, Tomas Gomez
- 324. "Forever and a Day" 1942 (Box 4)
  Claude Rains, Ian Hunter, Robert Cummings, Elsa lanchester
- 325. "Forever Female" (Box 4)
  Ginger Rogers, William Holden
- 326. "Fort Bowie" (Box 4)
  Ben Johnson, Jan Harrison
- 327. "Forty Thousand Horseman" (Box 4)
  Grant Taylor, Betty Bryant
- 328. "Four Daughters" (Box 4)
  May Robson, Claude Rains
- 329. "Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse" (Box 4)
  Rudolph Valentino, Alice Terry
- 330. "Four Sided Triangle" (Box 4)
  Barbara Payton, Stephen Murray
- 331. "Fourteen Hours" 1951 (Box 4)
  Richard Douglas, Paul Douglas, Barbara Bel Geddes
- 332. "The Fox" 1968 (Box 4)
  Anne Heywood, Carol Lynley, Sandy Dennis
- 333. "Frankenstein" (Box 4)
  Boris Karloff, Colin Clive, Mae Clark
- 334. "Frankenstein Meets the Wolfman" 1943 (Box 4)
- 335. "Frankenstein's Daughter" (Box 4)
  John Ashley, Sandra Knight
- 336. "Freckles" (Box 5)
  Martin West, Carol Christensen
- 337. "Free to Love" 1925 (Box 5)
  Clara Bow
- 338. "Freedom to Die" (Box 5)
  Paul Maxwell, Felicity Young
- 339. "Frenchman's Creek" (Box 5)
  Joan Fontaine, Arturo de Cordova
- 340. "Friends and Neighbors" 1962 (Box 5)
  Arthur Askey, Megs Jenkins
- 341. "From Russia With Love" (Box 5)
  Sean Connery, Daniela Bianchi
- 342. "From the Earth to the Moon" (Box 5)
  Joseph Cotten, George Sanders
- 343. "From This Day Forward" 1946 (Box 5)
  Joan Fontaine, Mark Stevens
- 344. "Front Page Women" (Box 5)
  Bette Davis, George Brent
- 345. "Frontier Badmen" 1943 (Box 5)
  William Farnum, Thomas Gomez, Diana Barrymore
- 346. "Gaby" (Box 5)
  Leslie Caron, John Kerr
- 347. "Galloping Dynamite" 1937 (Box 5)
  Kermit Maynard, Rocky the Wonder Horse
- 348. "The Garden of Allah"1936 (Box 5)
  Marlene Dietrich, Charles Boyer
- 349. "A Gathering of Eagles"1963 (Box 5)
  Rock Hudson, Rod Taylor
- 350. "Gaucho Lover"1935 (Box 5)
- 351. "The Gay '90's"1930 (Box 5)
  Claud Allister, Marion Davies
- 352. "General Crack" (Box 5)
  John Barrymore, Marion Nixon
- 353. "The Gentle Sex" (Box 5)
  Joan Greenwood, Lilli Palmer
- 354. "Georgy Girl"1966 (Box 5)
  James Mason, Lynn Redgrave, Alan Bates
- 355. "Ghost of the China Sea" (Box 5)
  David Brian
- 356. "The Girl of the Golden West" (Box 5)
  Nelson Eddy, Jeannette MacDonald
- 357. "The Girl Most Likely"1957 (Box 5)
  Jane Powell, Keith Andes, Kaye Ballard, Kelly Brown